#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/shubhkela (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

Financial Analysis
Public Speaking
Microsoft Excel

# Languages

English (Full Professional)

#### Certifications

Business Etiquette NCFM

Financial Markets: A Beginners' Module

Financing for Startup Businesses (Duke University)

Fundamentals of digital marketing Introduction to Operations Management (Wharton)

# Shubh Kela

Intern at SucSEED Venture Partners | Received PPO from ZS | NIT Raipur'21

Raipur

# Summary

I am currently in final year of study in Metallurgical and Materials Engineering, NIT Raipur. I believe in doing the right thing, and treating other people well, like my friends and I started a project siksha from scratch where I formed a team of 40 volunteer, we went to govt schools every weekend, and gave them quality education. I have worked in small as well big teams and shown good team management and leadership skills. I am quick learner & analytical thinker. Apart from this I have a keen interest in quizzing and have been an avid quizzer throughout my school and college life I am also part of my college's official quiz club and like play badminton and do a bit of photography in my free time.

# Experience

SucSEED Venture Partners

Intern

April 2020 - Present (5 months)

Worked with SucSEED ventures, venture capital firm on industry analysis reports, marketing campaigns as well as portfolio management.

www.sucseed.biz

Interact Club, NIT RAIPUR
Head coordinator
February 2017 - Present (3 years 7 months)
RAIPUR

Metallurgical Society, NIT Raipur General Secretary August 2018 - Present (2 years 1 month) Raipur

Dell

Teachers Trainer and Quiz Master

#### May 2018 - June 2020 (2 years 2 months)

Raipur, Chhattisgarh

I give teachers training on use of technology in education and host quiz for Dell Champs

### AAVARTAN, NIT Raipur

2 years 9 months

#### Core Team Lead

April 2018 - April 2020 (2 years 1 month)

**RAIPUR** 

#### Executive

May 2018 - April 2019 (1 year)

Raipur

#### Volunteer

August 2017 - May 2018 (10 months)

Raipur

### Project Siksha

#### Manager

May 2018 - December 2019 (1 year 8 months)

Raipur

### Faculty of Management Studies - University of Delhi

Intern

June 2019 - July 2019 (2 months)

Delhi, Delhi

I worked under Prof. Monica Singhania in the field of finance.

#### Indian Institute of Management Raipur

Intern

December 2018 - January 2019 (2 months)

Raipur, Chhattisgarh

I worked under professor Dr. Sumeet Gupta, Decision Science and operations on project researching sustainability of offline stores.

# Education

National Institute of Technology Raipur

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Metallurgical Engineering · (2017 - 2021)